OK, so just a brief word about the jet repository for this course.
The link within the resources here will take you to the master branch, which contains the finalized
source code everything that was typed and shown in the course in its final state.
And if you go to the dropdown here, there was another branch called Contribution Station Improvements.
And I created this branch in the case that anyone happens to find ways to improve the source code.
So if you do find something that can be improved, please feel free to message me with details and I'll
test it out as soon as I can and then add the changes to this branch here.
And if you'd like to get notifications about the course repository, just come here and adjust the watch
notifications.
OK?